Wolff, Sidney A. Arbitration Files 5131
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Neo Gravure Printing Company - New York Wholesale Grocers. (Box 22)
  - New York Quinine and Chemical Workers, Incorporated - United Chemical Workers of America Local 121, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - New York Post, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - New York 7 UP Bottling Company, Incorporated - Wage Reporting, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    June 1955
  - New York 7 UP Bottling Company, Incorporated - Soft Drink Workers Union Local 812, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - New York Subway Advertising Company, Incorporated - Local 153, Office Employees, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - New York State Mediation Board, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - New York Telephone - Communications Workers of America, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - New York Telephone Company - United Telephone Organizations, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - New York Telephone Company - Communication Workers (Dismissal of Carlo Caci), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - New York Wholesale Grocers Association - Local 1381, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1941-1943 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - New York Wholesale Grocers Association - Local 1381, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - New York Wholesale Grocers Association - Local 1381, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - New York Wholesale Grocers, Association - Local 1381, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1941-1946 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - New York Wholesale Grocers Association - Local 1381, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1946-1955 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- News Syndicate Company - Paul Kunian, Inc.. (Box 23)
  - News Syndicate Co. Inc. Newspaper Guild, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - North American Philips Co. Inc. Dist. 15 I.A.M., 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - North East Airlines - ALPA, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Airlines - Stewarders, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Airlines - Brotherhood Railways + Steamship Workers, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - North West Airlines, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nobelhart Mfg. Co. Internal Printing Pressmans Assistants Union - Local 447 (Mediation Board-), 1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. - Lodge 609 I.A.M. Fed. Med. Soc., 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical - I.A.M., 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Underwood - Olivetti - Union - Local 459, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Otis Elevator - Local 453 - I.U.E.R.M.W.A. - NY. St. Med. Bd., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Otis Elevator Company with International Union of Electrical Radio + Machine Workers, CIO, Local 453, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Otis Elevator Company, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Oxford Textile Finishing Co. - Textile Workers of America, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Oxford Textile Refinishing Co., 1962 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Package Machinery Co. - Local 220, I.U.E. AFL-CIO, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Packard Motor Car Company with Local 259, U.A.W.A., 1950 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Pan-American World Airways - T.W.U. National Mediation Boards, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Pan American World Airways - T.W.U. National Mediation Board, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Pan Am. T.W.U. - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Referee Sidney A. Wolff, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Pan-American - ALPA, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Pan-American - Brotherhood, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Pan-American - I.B.T.-, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Park Avenue Theater W. Local 306, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Park Avenue theater with Local 306, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Pathe Film Laboratories - MPLT. Local 701, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Pathe Laboratories, Inc. with Motion Picture Laboratory Technicians Union Local 702, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Paul Kunian Inc. - Local 65 - AAA, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Pennsylvania Railroad - Proctor and Gamble Co.. (Box 24)
- Proctor and Gamble Co. - Publishers Association of N.Y.. (Box 25)
  - Meeting Between the Executive Committee of the Procter and Gamble Independent Union and a Committee of the Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Bound. February 2, 1951
  - Procter and Gamble Independent Union - Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Procter and Gamble Independent Union - Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Bound. Appears heavily water damaged.
  - Procter and Gamble Independent Union - Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company - United Office and Professional Workers; Morning Telegraph - Newspaper Guild, Local 3; Thermoid Company - United Rubber; Prudential Insurance Company - United Office and Professional Workers, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Prudential Insurance Company - United Office and Professional Workers, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Bound. June 20, 1946
  - Prudential Insurance Company - Insurance Agents International Union, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Prudential Insurance Company - Insurance Agents International Union (Termination of Agent Minto), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    April 1957
  - Post - New York Typographical Union 6, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - United Steelworkers of America - Pottstown Metal Products, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Company - Utility Coworkers Association, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Quaker Oats Co. - Rose Frame and Mirror Works Inc.. (Box 26)
  - Quaker Oats Co. -Local 221-, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Leo Racoff with District 65 RWDSU, CIO, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Radio City Bar + Grill with Local 16, Hotel + Restaurant Workers Union, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Railway Express Agency - I.B.T., 1956 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Railway Express - Local 456 I.B.T., 1964 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Railway Express Agency, Inc. - I.B.T., 1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Raybestos - Manhattan Inc. - Manhattan Rubber Workers Inc. Unions, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Raygram Corporation - Amalgamated Union No. 15, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Realty Advisory Board with Local 164, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Robert Reiner, Inc. with Local 401, UERMWA, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Remington Rand - Local 344 I.U.E., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Remington Rand - Sherry Rand Corp. + I.U.E., Local 459, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Remington Arms Co. - Industrial Machine Office Workers Union, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Arnold Reuben Inc. Local 89, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Reuben's - (58th Street) - Waiters, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Reuben's 57st Corp. - Local 13, Office Employees Int. Union, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Rex Electric Mfg. Corp. - Local 485 - I.U.E.R.M.W.A., 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Reynolds Metals Co.- Local 7098, Dist. 9 USA, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Riegel Paper Corp. + United Paper Makers + Workers AFL-CIO - Local 712, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Riverbank Wine Co. Inc. - Local 18, Wholesale, Wine Salesmen's Union, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Robertshaw. Fulton Controls Company Fulton Sylphon Division with Federal Labor Union No. 21, 754, AFL, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller Center Inc. - Bldg. Constr. Trades Council - N.Y. Med. Bd., 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - John Rubeling Co., 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Rosanna Knitted Sportswear - Dist. 65 AAA, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Rose Frame + Mirror Works Inc. - Local 475 - Amalgamated. Machine, Instrument, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Roth-Getzoff Inc. - ShopRite Super Markets. (Box 27)
  - Roth-Getzoff Incorporated - Wholesale and Warehouse Employees Union; Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union Local 65 - Schwab Rubber Company, Incorporated and Schwab Latex Company, Incorporated, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    1947 and undated
  - Royal Typewriter Company, Incorporated - Royal Industrial Union Local 265, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Raynor Construction Company - Local 964, United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ruderman, Incorporated - United Optical Workers Union Local 408, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rupert Brothers - Brewery Workers Local Union 23 (New York), 1950-1951 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sagamore Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Saint James Restaurant - Bartenders Union Local 15, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - J.B. Salterini Company, Incorporated - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Local 475, 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Joe Salwen Paper Products Corporation - Local 447, International Printing Pressmen, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Ace Sample Card Company, Incorporated Board of Trade - District 65, Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers Union, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Saint Regis Paper Company - Local 1155, International Chemical Workers Union, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Saint Regis Paper Company - International Association of Machinists Lodge 64, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Short Hand Reporters, 1951-1952 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Herbert Sanson - Paul Fromm and the Federation of Shorthand Reporters, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Saymont Optical Instrument Company - Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - F and M Shaefer Brewing Company - Local 1059, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Schenectady Railway Arbitration - Transport Workers Union, Local 159, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Schenectady Railway Arbitration - Transport Workers Union, Local 159, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Schenck Transportation Company - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees Local 1061, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - A. Schrader's Son - Local 458, International Union of Electrical, 1959-1964 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Louis Schrag, Incorporated - Building Service Employees International Union, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - D.A. Schulte, 1950-1953 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Seaboard World Airlines, Incorporated - Air Line Pilots Association, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Seaboard and Western Airlines - Air Line Pilots Association, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Feinbart Realty Corporation - Local 2, New York State Independent Union, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Sharpless Corporation, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Shein's Department Store - Local 830, Retail and Wholesale Employees Union, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Sherman Square, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Sherwin-Williams Company - Paintmakers Local 1310, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Shop Rite Super Markets - Local 1262, Retail Clerks International Association, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Silk Association Inc. - Sylvania Electric Products. (Box 28)
  - Sulk Association of the Fur Industry, Inc. with Local 64, Joint Board Fur Dressers + Dyers Union, International Fur + Leather Workers Union, CIO, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Simplicity Pattern Co - Local 16 U.O.P.W.A., 1947 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Simplicity Pattern Co. - Local 16 U.O.P.W.A., 1947 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sinclair Refining - Bulk Distributing Plant Employees Union, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Singer Mfg. CO. with Local 401 UERMWA, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Singer Manufacturing Co. U.E.R.M.W.A. - Local 401 Mediation Board, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Singer Manufacturing Co. - Local 401 U.E.R.M.W.A., 1948 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company with Local 461 I.U.E.R.M.U. CIO, 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Singer Manufacturing Company with Local 401, UERMWA, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Singer Manufacturing Co. - I.U.E. Local 461, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Skydyne Inc. T.W.U., 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Slater System, Inc. with United Steel Workers of America (Local 2067), 1949 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - N.G. Slater Corp. with Local 64 Plastic Section, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Son Chief Electronics - Local 212 I.U.E. Amer. Arb., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Sonotone Corporation with Local 428, U.E.R.M.W.A., CIO, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Spector Freight System, Inc. - Local 707 I.B.T., 1962 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sperry - Rand - Local 450 I.U.E.R.M.W. - CIO, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Co. - Local 470, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Sperry I.U.E., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Staats Herold Corporation with Newspaper Guild of New York, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Standard Brands Inc. with Yeastmakers _ Distillery Local 42, CIO United Brewery + Soft Drink Workers of America, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Standard Kiel Mediation Board, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - The Stanley Works Local 1249 I.A.M., 1962-1965 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - The Stanley Works - Lodge 1249, I.A.M., 1965 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Star Bus Lines, Inc. - Local 252, Transport Workers, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Stuart-Dean Co. Inc. with Local 8 Metal Polishers Buffers + Platers + Helpers International Union AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Stewart Stamping Company with Local 453, I.U.E. CIO, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Stuhmer Baking Co. with Local 802 Bakery + Pastry Drivers, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65 -and- Suspender and Garter Manufacturers Association, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Supreme Knitting Machine Co. Inc. - Local 475 UERMWA, 1946-1948 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Supreme Furniture Mfg. Co. Inc., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Suzanne Pleshette Hearing, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Sylvania Electric Products - Local 617 IBT, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- TWA - Times Square Stores Corporation. (Box 29)
  - Trans World Airlines - Transport Workers Union, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Trans World Airlines - Transport Workers Union, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Technical Film Laboratories - Local 702, Motion Picture Laboratories Technicians, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Technical Materials - Local 1783, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Texas Company - Oil Workers International Union Local 12-638, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Texas Company - Local 13-632, Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Texas Company - Local 14-539, Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1957-1959 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Theater Guild - Actors Equity Association, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, Retail and Wholesale Employees Union, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    October 8, 1947. Bound.
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, United Retail and Wholesale Department Store Employees Association, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Bound. November 22, 1946. 1 of 2.
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, United Retail and Wholesale Department Store Employees Association, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Bound. November 22, 1946. 2 of 2.
- Times Square Stores Corporation - Voland and Sons, Inc.. (Box 30)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation, Seedman Company Incorporated, and Gotham Products Corporation - Retail and Wholesale Employees Union Local 830, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    March 19, 1948. Bound.
  - Times Square Stores - Arbitration, 1946-1948 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, Retail and Wholesale Employees Union, 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, United Retail and Wholesale Department Store Employees Association, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Local 830, United Retail and Wholesale Department Store Employees Association, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Times Square Stores Corporation - Notes, Memos on Original Wage Arbitration, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Titan Metal Manufacturing - Local 1282, United Auto Workers, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Mostel, Zero - Toby Cole, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Trageser Copper Works, Incorporated - Independent Employees Association, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Trane Company - United Association of Journeymen Local 730, 1958-1959 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Trans-Lux Theatres Corporation - Local 306, Moving Picture Machine Operators Union, 1949-1952 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Trans World Airlines, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Troy Fuel Oil Company Incorporated - Amalgamated Union Local 355, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Truck and Trailer Industries, Incorporated and Commercial Auto Painting and Lettering, Incorporated - Amalgamated Local 259, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - 205 West 39th Street Corporation - Bartenders' Union Local 15, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Underwood Corporation - International Union of Electrical Local 267, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Underwood Corporation - Local 459, International Union of Electrical Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Underwood Corporation - Local 267, International Union of Electrical Workers, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Underwood Corporation - United Traction Company. (Box 31)
  - Underwood Corp. - I.A.M. Lodge 350, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Underwood Corp. - I.U.E. Local 267, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Underwood Corp. - I.A.M. Lodge 350, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Underwood Corporation with I.U.E. Local 267, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Underwood Corp. - Local 267 I.U.E. -, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - United Press Association with American Newspaper Guild, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Underwood Corp. - I.U.E. Local 267 -AAA-, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Union News Co. with News Distribution Employees Unions Local 906, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Union News Company with Local 539 Luncheonette + Soda Fountain Workers Union, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Union News Co. - News Distr. Empl. Union Local 906, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Union News Co. with Local 906 News Distribution Employees Union, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Union News Company with Wholesale, Retail + Warehouse Workers Union, Local 906, 1950-1951 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Union News Co. Chain Service Restaurant + Luncheonette + Soda Fountain Workers, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc. -and- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 804, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - United Parcel Service - Local 804 United Delivery drivers and Employees, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Tool Company, Inc. with Local 407 UERMWA, CIO, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - United Press, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - United Restaurant Liquor Dealers of Manhattan Inc. with Local 15 Bartenders Union of New York City, 1948-1949 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - United States Rubber Company with T.W.U.A. Fisk Cord Mills General, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - United Traction Company with AASERMCEA, Division B21, 1952-1953 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - United Traction - A.A.S.R.E.M.A. Notes + Drafts, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Misc., 1953 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Union Exhibits Nos. 1-32, 1949-1954 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- United Traction Company - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Co.. (Box 32)
  - United Traction Company - Division 1321, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America (Testimony), 1953 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Volumes 1-5
  - United Traction Company - Division 1321, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America (Testimony), 1953 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Volumes 6-9
  - United Traction Company - Division 1321, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway, and Motor Coach Employees of America (Testimony), 1953 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Volumes 10-13
  - Universal Pictures Company, Incorporated - Moving Picture Machine Operators Union, Local 306, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    August 11-12, 1948. Bound.
  - Utility Coworkers Association - Public Service Electric and Gas Company (Electric Operating Department), 1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Bound. March 27, 1956.
  - Valeria Bakery - District 50, United Mineworkers of America, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Vanleigh Furniture Company, Incorporated - Local 814, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Verney Mills - Textile Workers Union of America, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Varig Airlines - International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Viewlex, Incorporated - District 15, International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Viking Press, Incorporated - Local 18, Book and Magazine Guild, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Voland and Sons, Incorporated - Local 475, International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - WNHC TV - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - WPIX, Incorporated - Radio and Television Broadcast Engineers Union, Local 1212, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Walter A. Smith - Allstate Insurance Company, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Walter Company, Incorporated - Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Association, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Ward Baking Company - Bakery Drivers Local Union 550, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Washington Cemetery - Local 365, Cemetery Workers, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 675, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 780, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- West Virginia Pulp and Paper Co. - Western Union. (Box 33)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 675, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Manning Study for Recovery Department: A Report Prepared for West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Bound. May 16, 1960
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    January 18, 1961. Bound.
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    January 19, 1961. Bound.
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    January 4, 1961. Bound.
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    January 3, 1961. Bound.
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 675, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    June 17, 1958. Bound.
  - Welfare Fund 2, Local 138, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric Company, Incorporated - Communications Workers of America Installation Division Number 6, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    December 1-3, 1949. Bound.
  - Western Electric Company, Incorporated - Communications Workers of America Installation Division Number 6, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    June 16, 1950. Bound
  - Western Electric, 1950-1951 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Western Electric Company, Incorporated - Communications Workers of America, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Western Union Telegraph Company - Commercial Telegraphers Union, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Westinghouse Electric - Zylite Optical Company PLUS MISCELLANEOUS. (Box 34)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. Local 401 UERMW -AAA-, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - Local 617 - I.U.E.R.M.W. Amer. Arb., 1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - Westinghouse Conf. Bd., I.U.E., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Westinghouse Electric Local 746, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. - National Westinghouse Conference Board, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 5)